;------------------------------------------------------------------------------
; ';'로 주석을 시작합니다. 
; 대소문자는 구분하지 않으며 컴마(,)나 탭 혹은 공백으로 단어들을 구분합니다.
; 채팅중에 아래에 나열된 단어가 포함되어 있으면 막히게 됩니다.
; (와일드 카드는 필요 없습니다.)
;
; Any comment starts with ';'
; The list is not case-sensitive, and the words are separated by using comma, tab, or blank
; The chat is blocked when any of the words below are mentioned in the chat.
; (No need for the wild card)
;
;	주의!!  채팅 필터입니다!! 캐릭터 필터가 아닙니다!!
;
; Please be aware that this is the Chat Filter!!! Not a Character Filter!!! 
;
;------------------------------------------------------------------------------
